laemmle.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Laemmle.com

**Laemmle.com Privacy Statement**

(last update February 2011)

Laemmle.com, Inc. ("Laemmle.com") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our terms of use.

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other information pages on our site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. We strongly recommend that as you read this Privacy Policy, you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you.

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the UK laws but we will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. We will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to your information being transferred or used in this way please do not register or provide us with such information.

If you have any questions, send an email via [our contact form](http://www.laemmle.com/contact).

**Overview**

Your privacy is very important to us. As part of the normal operation of our services we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.

As described below, some of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to third parties, and such personally identifiable information is used by us and such third parties. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

**Information Collection, Use, Sharing and Disclosure**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website and services. Through customer surveys, subscriptions, and newsletter registration, our site may request users to give us contact, demographic and/or financial information (such as their name, locale, gender, age, ethnicity, income level, education level, marital status, parental status, primary language spoke in the home and email address). The demographic information is used, among other things, to enhance user experience so we can be more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new services and content, as well as for surveys and newsletters. Our site may use an order form for customers to subscribe to our for-pay services. 

We collect contact information (like e-mail address) and financial information (like account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send billing invoices. Contact information is also used to get in touch with the subscribers when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services and for in-house statistics. Specifically, in connection with fulfillment of your purchase, we may share your contact information and financial information with the movie theater chains at which you are attending screenings and for which you are purchasing admissions.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Information collected during Laemmle.com subscriber registration is used for, among other things, completing purchase transactions, in-house statistics, marketing target information, and advising clients of Laemmle.com news and information.

Laemmle.com collects demographic information in part for the purpose of assembling a pool of individuals who may be invited to market research screenings of movies and/or surveys produced by Laemmle.com clients, including movie studios and producers ("Studios"). Such Studios may request a certain demographic group to view a movie in a particular location, for research and/or test screening purposes, and Laemmle.com will make invitations to individuals chosen at random from the Laemmle.com customer pool which meet the demographic requirements for the desired location. Such demographic information is not used in any way to discriminate against any customers, but is solely used to assemble a test audience which meets the demographic requirements of the Studios for the movie. No information about identifiable individuals is provided to the Studios.

This site contains links to other sites. Laemmle.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or any website from which you may have linked to Laemmle.com.

Laemmle.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read this privacy policy to fully understand how we will make use of the personal information you share with us. Laemmle.com collects certain personal information in order to provide you with customized services, content, and advertisements. Some personal information is gathered when you register to receive certain Laemmle.com products or services. We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information contained in your registration data or related data, provided that, such information will NOT include personally identifying information, except as specifically authorized by you or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process, or to enforce the terms of service. In addition, we may provide your personally identifiable and personal financial information to third parties if you provide prior consent to the exchange of the information. Laemmle.com will also use your personal information for the purposes of providing you with any services to which you subscribe, and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees from you for those services, and notifying you or contacting you regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary for Laemmle.com to disclose your personal information to one or more agents and contractors of Laemmle.com and their subcontractors, but such agents, contractors, and subcontractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from Laemmle.com only for these purposes. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Laemmle.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your Laemmle.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Laemmle.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Laemmle.com reserves the right to change this statement at any time by posting revisions on the Laemmle.com web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of us.

We may run contests or sweepstakes on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their name and email address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, and/or income level). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary, such as if they win a contest or sweepstakes or to notify users of upcoming contests or sweepstakes. There are three primary types of contests or sweepstakes: (1.) We host solely and all information that is collected stays in-house. (2.) We may share address information with third party for shipping purposes. (3.) In some rare instances, a third party may host the contest or sweepstakes and all information is then shared. For customer inquiries about our information sharing practices please write to Laemmle.com, Inc., Customer Service, 2255 Glades Road, Suite 232W, Boca Raton, FL 33431. In our contest or sweepstakes registration, we give our users the opportunity to sign up for the Laemmle.com newsletter. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter. Laemmle.com products and services are directed at an adult market, and therefore this site is intended for use by adults only. Laemmle.com encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. Children of any age should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this web site by users under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

Some Laemmle.com services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both Laemmle.com, Inc. and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. These companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail via [our contact form](http://www.laemmle.com/contact).

Laemmle  
Customer Service  
11523 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

**Advertisements**

Ads appearing on this web site are delivered to you by either (a) one of our web advertising partners or (b) by us. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for instance) and whether or not you responded to the ad delivered, (but not your name, address, phone number or other personal information), is used to serve advertisements to you on this site. We may use your zip code or geographical location information to serve advertisements to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally, unless you have provided us with your prior consent to disclose such personally identifiable information. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are never disclosed to marketing advertisers without your consent.

This site may use its own proprietary ad serving system. However, this site may use and allow for third party ad serving systems (i.e.: Double-click, Mediaplex, Atlas, Zedo, etc.). Third party ad serving systems are approved at the site's discretion. The site and its third party servers collect and store anonymous data, typically through the use of cookies.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Public Forums**

This site may contain message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. We request users to give us contact information, such as name, email, address, occupation, and interests to be a registered bulletin board user. This information is optional and not necessary to post messages. This information may be used by the administrator to send the user email notices. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.

**Security**

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information transferred to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We use Secure Shell to access our servers remotely, and all server sessions are encrypted. We protect the secure areas of our site (including our databases and intranet) by using a commercial firewall.

**Choice/Opt-Out - Your Ability to Opt-Out and Remove Your Information**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service:

1.      Users can send email via our [contact form](http://www.laemmle.com/contact).

2.      Users can send mail to the following postal address:  
Laemmle  
Customer Service  
11523 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

4.      Users can call the following telephone number: 1-310-478-1041

**Correct/Update - Your Ability to Update Your Information**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. Users can [log in here](http://www.laemmle.com/account/login) to their pre-existing account and modify their personal data.
  2. Users can send mail to the following postal address:  
Laemmle  
Customer Service  
11325 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

Laemmle  
Customer Service  
11523 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

or email via our [feedback form](http://www.laemmle.com/contact).
